♪♪♪
♪ AYY ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN FUCKIN'
HOES AND POPPIN' PILLIES ♪
♪ MAN, I FEEL JUST LIKE
A ROCKSTAR (STAR) ♪
♪ AYY, AYY, ALL MY
BROTHERS GOT THAT GAS ♪
♪ AND THEY ALWAYS BE
SMOKIN' LIKE A RASTA ♪
♪ FUCKIN' WITH ME,
CALL UP ON A UZI ♪
♪ AND SHOW UP, MAN
THEM THE SHOTTAS ♪
♪ WHEN MY HOMIES PULL
UP ON YOUR BLOCK ♪
♪ THEY MAKE THAT THING GO
GRRRA-TA-TA-TA (POW, POW, POW)♪
♪ AYY, AYY, SWITCH MY
WHIP, CAME BACK IN BLACK ♪
♪ I'M STARTIN' SAYIN', "REST
IN PEACE TO BON SCOTT" ♪
♪ AYY, CLOSE THAT DOOR,
WE BLOWIN' SMOKE ♪
♪ SHE ASK ME LIGHT A
FIRE LIKE I'M MORRISON ♪
♪ AYY, ACT A FOOL ON STAGE ♪
♪ PROLLY LEAVE MY FUCKIN'
SHOW IN A COP CAR ♪
♪ AYY, SHIT WAS LEGENDARY ♪
♪ THREW A TV OUT THE
WINDOW OF THE MONTAGE ♪
♪ COCAINE ON THE TABLE, LIQUOR
POURIN', DON'T GIVE A DAMN ♪
♪ DUDE, YOUR GIRLFRIEND IS A
GROUPIE, SHE JUST TRYNA GET IN ♪
♪ SAYIN', "I'M WITH THE BAND" ♪
♪ AYY, AYY, NOW SHE
ACTIN' OUTTA POCKET ♪
♪ TRYNA GRAB UP
FROM MY PANTS ♪
♪ HUNDRED BITCHES IN MY TRAILER
SAY THEY AIN'T GOT A MAN ♪
♪ AND THEY ALL
BROUGHT A FRIEND ♪
♪ YEAH, AYY ♪
♪ AYY, I'VE BEEN FUCKIN'
HOES AND POPPIN' PILLIES ♪
♪ MAN, I FEEL JUST LIKE
A ROCKSTAR (STAR) ♪
♪ AYY, AYY, ALL MY
BROTHERS GOT THAT GAS ♪
♪ AND THEY ALWAYS BE
SMOKIN' LIKE A RASTA ♪
♪ FUCKIN' WITH ME,
CALL UP ON A UZI ♪
♪ AND SHOW UP, MAN
THEM THE SHOTTAS ♪
♪ WHEN MY HOMIES PULL
UP ON YOUR BLOCK ♪
♪ THEY MAKE THAT THING GO
GRRRA-TA-TA-TA (POW, POW, POW)♪
♪ I'VE BEEN IN THE HILLS
FUCKIN' SUPERSTARS ♪
♪ FEELIN' LIKE A POP
STAR (21, 21, 21) ♪
♪ DRANKIN' HENNY, BAD BITCHES
JUMPIN' IN THE POOL ♪
♪ AND THEY AIN'T
GOT ON NO BRA ♪
♪ HIT HER FROM THE BACK,
PULLIN' ON HER TRACKS ♪
♪ AND NOW SHE SCREAMIN' OUT,
"NO MáS" (YEAH, YEAH, YEAH) ♪
♪ THEY LIKE, "SAVAGE, WHY
YOU GOT A 12 CAR GARAGE ♪
♪ AND YOU ONLY
GOT 6 CARS?" (21) ♪
♪ I AIN'T WITH THE CAKIN' ♪
♪ HOW YOU KISS
THAT? (KISS THAT?) ♪
♪ YOUR WIFEY SAY
I'M LOOKIN' ♪
♪ LIKE A WHOLE SNACK
(BIG SNACK) ♪
♪ GREEN HUNDREDS
IN MY SAFE ♪
♪ I GOT OLD RACKS
(OLD RACKS) ♪
♪ L.A. BITCHES ALWAYS
ASKIN' WHERE THE COKE AT ♪
♪ LIVIN' LIKE A ROCKSTAR ♪
♪ SMASH OUT ON A COP CAR ♪
♪ SWEETER THAN
A POP-TART, ♪
♪ YOU KNOW YOU
ARE NOT HARD ♪
♪ I DONE MADE THE HOT CHART ♪
♪ 'MEMBER I USED
TO TRAP HARD ♪
♪ LIVIN' LIKE A ROCKSTAR ♪
♪ I'M LIVIN' LIKE A ROCKSTAR ♪
♪ AYY, I'VE BEEN FUCKIN'
HOES AND POPPIN' PILLIES ♪
♪ MAN, I FEEL JUST LIKE
A ROCKSTAR (STAR) ♪
♪ AYY, AYY, ALL MY
BROTHERS GOT THAT GAS ♪
♪ AND THEY ALWAYS BE
SMOKIN' LIKE A RASTA ♪
♪ FUCKIN' WITH ME,
CALL UP ON A UZI ♪
♪ AND SHOW UP, MAN
THEM THE SHOTTAS ♪
♪ WHEN MY HOMIES PULL
UP ON YOUR BLOCK ♪
♪ THEY MAKE THAT THING GO
GRRRA-TA-TA-TA (POW, POW, POW)♪
♪ ROCKSTAR ♪
♪ FEEL JUST LIKE A ROCK ♪
♪ STAR ♪
♪ ROCKSTAR ♪
♪ FEEL JUST LIKE A ROCK ♪
♪♪♪